<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review on Sparkly Alpaca</title>
    <link>https://lucy778.github.io/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on Sparkly Alpaca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lucy778.github.io/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Clio Sharp So Simple Waterproof Pencil Liner and Dose of Colors Pencil Eyeliners</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-clio-dose-colors-pencil-liners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-clio-dose-colors-pencil-liners/</guid>
      <description>These are both super skinny retractable pencil liners. The Clio one is a bit skinnier than the Dose of Colors one but they are both tiny. So let&amp;rsquo;s start with the use case of these things. You&amp;rsquo;re on the way to work or some important date or social event, and you didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to apply liner at home before you left. Because sleep is important, dammit.
For this use case, this type of liner is perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morphe x Pony 35I Icy Fantasy Palette is cute but not for everyone</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-morphe-x-pony-icy-fantasy-palette-351/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-morphe-x-pony-icy-fantasy-palette-351/</guid>
      <description>I have never purchased a Morphe product before this palette because I always found the shade duplication off putting. It looks like they are moving away from that type of palette, since they are discontinuing a bunch of the palettes which are basically 35 shades of brown.
I have also never bought a Pony collaboration because none of them have really been that interesting.
The concept for this Icy Fantasy Palette is awesome though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OMG I love  Ashley Kaltwasser and Adam Bonilla</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/omg-i-love-ashley-kaltwasser-and-adam-bonilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/omg-i-love-ashley-kaltwasser-and-adam-bonilla/</guid>
      <description>I found about Ashley because of her side hustle(main hustle?) as a fitness model, not so much because of her IFBB bikini pro bodybuilding and Olympia accolades. Since I watch allll the glute workout videos, I watched her glute videos, and I thought she had an awesome attitude. She is so bubbly and motivated and fun. Her coach, Adam Bonilla, is super smart, sensible, and low stress.
They started this “Bikini and the Brain” podcast together towards the end of last year where they talk about their experiences with pro bikini bodybuilding competitions and address common questions and misconceptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The problem with Lip Tints: Review of Peripera Airy Ink Velvet Lip Tint</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-peripera-air-tint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-peripera-air-tint/</guid>
      <description>What is Peripera Ink Airy Velvet Lip Tint? It&amp;rsquo;s basically a moussey lipstick which stains your lips. You can wear it like a liquid lipstick or remove it and just leave the tint.
How does it look? See the pics :)
Shade: #3 Sold Out Red. This is a cool red with a matte appearance. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t emphasise lip lines, it is super smoothing.
How does it wear? The Tint is long lasting but the liquid lipstick is not and has a tendency to smear and transfer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>