<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fitness on Sparkly Alpaca</title>
    <link>https://lucy778.github.io/tags/fitness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fitness on Sparkly Alpaca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lucy778.github.io/tags/fitness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to motivate yourself to work out at home?</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/the-home-workout-struggle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/the-home-workout-struggle/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a lot luckier than some people when it comes to home gym equipment. I have some adjustable dumbbells already, and even the resistance bands I preordered online have arrived. But despite this, my workout routine has collapsed.
For me, gym wasn&amp;rsquo;t about doing something. It was about going somewhere. Just the act of going there makes the rest so much easier. You&amp;rsquo;re there, at the gym, to lift weights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OMG I love  Ashley Kaltwasser and Adam Bonilla</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/omg-i-love-ashley-kaltwasser-and-adam-bonilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/omg-i-love-ashley-kaltwasser-and-adam-bonilla/</guid>
      <description>I found about Ashley because of her side hustle(main hustle?) as a fitness model, not so much because of her IFBB bikini pro bodybuilding and Olympia accolades. Since I watch allll the glute workout videos, I watched her glute videos, and I thought she had an awesome attitude. She is so bubbly and motivated and fun. Her coach, Adam Bonilla, is super smart, sensible, and low stress.
They started this “Bikini and the Brain” podcast together towards the end of last year where they talk about their experiences with pro bikini bodybuilding competitions and address common questions and misconceptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I am not a fan of Jeff nippard</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/why-i-am-not-a-fan-of-jeff-nippard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/why-i-am-not-a-fan-of-jeff-nippard/</guid>
      <description>I am not gonna put any qualifiers or disclaimers here. Bad advice is bad advice, even if there is far worse out there.
I am also not going to do a deep dive and watch 50 videos from this guy to give some thorough, comprehensive review. I have seen enough.
I watched his “Is Workout Volume Actually Killing Your Gains? (Athlean-X Response)” video which came up in my youtube recommendations, probably because I am a fan of Athlean-X.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>