<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sparkly Alpaca</title>
    <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sparkly Alpaca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lucy778.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What products should I use for scalp psoriasis?</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/dry-scalp-treatments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/dry-scalp-treatments/</guid>
      <description>If you have scalp itchiness then one of the common causes is psoriasis. This means you get dry, scaly patches on your scalp.
There are other causes of scalp dryness and itchiness like seborrheic dermatitis and dandruff. I’m going to focus on psoriasis because this is what I have and what I know about.
But the advice for moisturizing scalp applies for anyone with dry scalp. General scalp dryness and itchiness and advice is discussed below – click HERE to skip ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I know I’m getting enough iron?</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/all-about-iron/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/all-about-iron/</guid>
      <description>I’m researching iron at the moment because I have iron deficiency problems. Sources used will be linked as they come up.
Here is the lowdown on iron in a Q&amp;amp;A format:
How much iron do you have in your body? Healthy people have 4-5 grams of iron in their body The amount is approx. 38 mg iron/kg body weight for women and 50 mg iron/kg body for men.
Where is iron used in your body?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why keto diets are garbage</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/the-keto-conspiracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/the-keto-conspiracy/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I have done some experimenting with keto baking. To say that I am bitterly disappointed is an understatement.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also done some Coursera courses on nutrition and exercise science. This has crystallised my thoughts into the following:
&amp;ldquo;Keto is an overhyped, money-making sham.&amp;rdquo;
Let me defend this opinion.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with what keto is good for. Obviously, it is good for epileptics, as this is what it was originally designed for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephanie buttermore is a legend &lt;3</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/stephanie-buttermore-and-diet-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/stephanie-buttermore-and-diet-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Some months ago now, I talked about Stephanie Buttermore’s “all in” dieting approach. Basically, she recognised that she had very disordered eating and hunger signals. This was having a knock on effect on her overall health, especially her hormone levels.
She decided to follow a diet where she would eat at least 2500 calories a day, with no upper limit to get her hunger, weight, and health back to normal levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to do makeup like Hindash</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/how-to-do-makeup-like-hindash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/how-to-do-makeup-like-hindash/</guid>
      <description>Who is Hindash? This is the nom de guerre of Mohammed Hindash, a makeup artist based in Dubai, Arab Emirates. I don’t know much about him to be honest, but I know that his makeup is red hot fire, his voice is calming, and his tutorials are crisp, clean and well narrated. His dog is also adorable. 🐶
His makeup style is very neutral and minimal. His makeup is definitely Arab-inspired, as he loves to play up the eyes with wings and inner corner cat eyeliner, however it is much more pared back than classic Arab makeup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to motivate yourself to work out at home?</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/the-home-workout-struggle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/the-home-workout-struggle/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a lot luckier than some people when it comes to home gym equipment. I have some adjustable dumbbells already, and even the resistance bands I preordered online have arrived. But despite this, my workout routine has collapsed.
For me, gym wasn&amp;rsquo;t about doing something. It was about going somewhere. Just the act of going there makes the rest so much easier. You&amp;rsquo;re there, at the gym, to lift weights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moogoo Skin Milk Udder Cream Review is a fab day moisturiser</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-moogoo-moisturiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-moogoo-moisturiser/</guid>
      <description>Moogoo is an Australian brand of moisturiser with natural ingredients. The skin milk udder cream moisturiser is Moogoo&amp;rsquo;s original, headliner product, but they have expanded their line to include other variations e.g. full cream version for drier skin, MSM version for rosacea etc.
This moisturiser has a light texture and absorbs relatively quickly for a moisturiser. It has a slightly tacky finish soon after application and then will eventually dry down to a natural, non-shiny finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Clio Sharp So Simple Waterproof Pencil Liner and Dose of Colors Pencil Eyeliners</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-clio-dose-colors-pencil-liners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-clio-dose-colors-pencil-liners/</guid>
      <description>These are both super skinny retractable pencil liners. The Clio one is a bit skinnier than the Dose of Colors one but they are both tiny. So let&amp;rsquo;s start with the use case of these things. You&amp;rsquo;re on the way to work or some important date or social event, and you didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to apply liner at home before you left. Because sleep is important, dammit.
For this use case, this type of liner is perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to choose an eyelash curler which works for your eye shape and doesn&#39;t pinch your eyelid</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/how-can-i-stop-eyelash-curlers-pinching-my-eye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/how-can-i-stop-eyelash-curlers-pinching-my-eye/</guid>
      <description>There is a very cool post on Reddit which talks about how you can measure the dimensions of eyelash curlers and your eye to ensure they match up. It&amp;rsquo;s based on this nerdy and awesome blog post by Nikki Gilland (also see her more recent update here).
This is pretty important since if you&amp;rsquo;ve used a curler you will know that the wrong sized eyelash curler can pinch your eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morphe x Pony 35I Icy Fantasy Palette is cute but not for everyone</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-morphe-x-pony-icy-fantasy-palette-351/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-morphe-x-pony-icy-fantasy-palette-351/</guid>
      <description>I have never purchased a Morphe product before this palette because I always found the shade duplication off putting. It looks like they are moving away from that type of palette, since they are discontinuing a bunch of the palettes which are basically 35 shades of brown.
I have also never bought a Pony collaboration because none of them have really been that interesting.
The concept for this Icy Fantasy Palette is awesome though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OMG I love  Ashley Kaltwasser and Adam Bonilla</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/omg-i-love-ashley-kaltwasser-and-adam-bonilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/omg-i-love-ashley-kaltwasser-and-adam-bonilla/</guid>
      <description>I found about Ashley because of her side hustle(main hustle?) as a fitness model, not so much because of her IFBB bikini pro bodybuilding and Olympia accolades. Since I watch allll the glute workout videos, I watched her glute videos, and I thought she had an awesome attitude. She is so bubbly and motivated and fun. Her coach, Adam Bonilla, is super smart, sensible, and low stress.
They started this “Bikini and the Brain” podcast together towards the end of last year where they talk about their experiences with pro bikini bodybuilding competitions and address common questions and misconceptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I am not a fan of Jeff nippard</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/why-i-am-not-a-fan-of-jeff-nippard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/why-i-am-not-a-fan-of-jeff-nippard/</guid>
      <description>I am not gonna put any qualifiers or disclaimers here. Bad advice is bad advice, even if there is far worse out there.
I am also not going to do a deep dive and watch 50 videos from this guy to give some thorough, comprehensive review. I have seen enough.
I watched his “Is Workout Volume Actually Killing Your Gains? (Athlean-X Response)” video which came up in my youtube recommendations, probably because I am a fan of Athlean-X.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The problem with Lip Tints: Review of Peripera Airy Ink Velvet Lip Tint</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-peripera-air-tint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/review-of-peripera-air-tint/</guid>
      <description>What is Peripera Ink Airy Velvet Lip Tint? It&amp;rsquo;s basically a moussey lipstick which stains your lips. You can wear it like a liquid lipstick or remove it and just leave the tint.
How does it look? See the pics :)
Shade: #3 Sold Out Red. This is a cool red with a matte appearance. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t emphasise lip lines, it is super smoothing.
How does it wear? The Tint is long lasting but the liquid lipstick is not and has a tendency to smear and transfer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://lucy778.github.io/post/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucystreams&#43;beautyblog@gmail.com (Lucy Rebekah)</author>
      <guid>https://lucy778.github.io/post/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Lucy and I have started this blog because basically, I spend a lot of time and money on make up and I want to channel my obssession into something more productive than just browsing instagram, youtube and reddit.
I want to share my thoughts on my favourite and not so favourite make up and beauty trends.
I know I&amp;rsquo;ve missed the blogging hype train by oh, about 10 years or so, but this is something I&amp;rsquo;ve never personally done and I thought it would be fun.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>